Guide to the Centro de Accion Social Autonomo Papers, 1963-1978
Department of Special Collections
- SERIES I: CASA ADMINISTRATIVE RECORDS, 1968 -1978
  - Subseries F. Sin Fronteras Commission
    - Production Subcommittee, Peoples Translation Service, press packets, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Production Subcommittee, photograph logs, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Production Subcommittee, production records, Jan.-Sept. 1976 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Production Subcommittee, production records, Oct. 1976 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Production Subcommittee, production records, Nov. 1976 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Production Subcommittee, production records, Dec. 1976-Feb. 1977 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Production Subcommittee, production records, Mar.-May 1977 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, Oct. 1975 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, Nov. 1975 (1) (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, Nov. 1975 (2) (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, Dec. 1975 (1) (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, Dec. 1975 (2) (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, Jan. 1976 (1) (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, Jan. 1976 (2) (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, Feb. 1976 (1) (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, Feb. 1976 (2) (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, Feb. 1976 (3) (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, Mar. 1976 (1) (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, Mar. 1976 (2) (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, Mar. 1976 (3) (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, Apr. 1976 (1) (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, Apr. 1976 (2) (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, Apr. 1976 (3) (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, May 1976 (1) (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, May 1976 (2) (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, June 1976 (1) (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, June 1976 (2) (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, June 1976 (3) (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, July 1976 (1) (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, July 1976(2) (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, July 1976(3) (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, July 1976(4) (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, Aug. 1976 (1) (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, (Aug. 1976 2) (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, Aug. 1976(3) (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, Aug. 1976(4) (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, Sept. 1976 (1) (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, Sept. 1976(2) (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, Sept. 1976(3) (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, Sept. 1976(4) (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, (2) (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, (3) (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, Nov. 1976 (1) (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, (2) (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, (3) (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, (4) (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, Dec. 1976 (1) (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, (2) (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Production Subcommittee, story drafts, (3) (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Production Subcommittee, miscellany, 1975-1976 (1) (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Production Subcommittee, miscellany, (2) (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Production Subcommittee, miscellany, (3) (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Production Subcommittee, miscellany, Feb. 1977 (1) (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Production Subcommittee, miscellany, (2) (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Production Subcommittee, miscellany, (3) (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Production Subcommittee, miscellany, (4) (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Production Subcommittee, miscellany, Apr. 1977 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Production Subcommittee, miscellany, June 1977 (1) (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Production Subcommittee, miscellany, (2) (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Production Subcommittee, miscellany, (3) (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Production Subcommittee, miscellany, (4) (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Production Subcommittee, miscellany, July 1977 (1) (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Production Subcommittee, miscellany, (2) (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Production Subcommittee, miscellany, (3) (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Production Subcommittee, miscellany, Aug. 1977 (1) (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Production Subcommittee, miscellany, (2) (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Production Subcommittee, miscellany, (3) (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Production Subcommittee, miscellany, (4) (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Production Subcommittee, miscellany, Mar. 1978 (1) (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Production Subcommittee, miscellany, (2) (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Production Subcommittee, miscellany, (3) (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Production Subcommittee, miscellany, (4) (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Production Subcommittee, miscellany, Apr.-May 1978 (1) (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Production Subcommittee, miscellany, (2) (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Production Subcommittee, miscellany, (4) (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Production Subcommittee, miscellany, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Production Subcommittee, miscellany, n.d. (1) (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Production Subcommittee, miscellany, n.d. (2) (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Subseries G. Worker and Union Affairs Commission
    - Worker and Union Affairs Commission, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Subseries H. Local Casa Organizations
    - Chicago Local Committee, 1974-1977 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Estudiantil Nucleo, 1975-1977 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Greeley Local Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Joaquín Murrieta Nucleo, 1976-1977 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Los Angeles Local Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Los Angeles Local Committee, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Los Angeles Local Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Los Angeles Local Committee, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Los Angeles Local Committee, financial records, 1975-1976 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Los Angeles Local Committee, internal bulletins, 1975-1977 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Luisa Moreno Nucleo, 1975-1976 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Miguel Enríquez Nucleo, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Oakland Local Committee, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Oakland Local Committee 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Oakland Local Committee n.d. (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Oakland Local Committee, financial records, 1975-1976 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Primero de Mayo (Santa Barbara) Local Committee, 1975-1977 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Ricardo F. Magón Nucleo, 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - San Antonio Local Committee, 1975-1977 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - San Antonio Local Committee, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - San Antonio Local Committee, financial records, 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - San Diego Nucleo, 1975-1977 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - San Jose Nucleo, 1974-1976 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - San Jose Nucleo, 1977-1978 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Santa Ana Center, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Seattle Nucleo, 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Seattle Nucleo, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Seattle Nucleo, financial records, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Seattle Nucleo, "La Expresión," 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Teatro Nucleo, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Subseries G. Papers of Antonio Rodriguez (Casa Officer)
    - Correspondence, notes and miscellany, 1968-1974 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, notes and miscellany, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, notes and miscellany, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, notes and miscellany, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, notes and miscellany, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Notes, n.d. (1) (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Notes, n.d. (2) (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Notes, n.d. (3) (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Notes, n.d. (4) (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Notes (notebook), n.d. (1) (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Notes (notebook), n.d. (2) (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Notes (notebook), n.d. (3) (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Notes (notebook), n.d. (4) (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Notes (notebook), n.d. (5) (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Notes (notebook), n.d. (6) (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Notes (notebook), n.d. (7) (Box 24, Folder 7)
- SERIES II: FEDEREAL BUREAU OF INVESTIGATION REPORTS ON CASA, 1972 -1978
  - Correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda and reports, Apr.-Nov. 1972 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Memoranda and reports, Jan.-Dec. 1973 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Memoranda and reports, Jan.-June 1974 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Memoranda and reports, Aug.-Dec. 1974 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Memoranda and reports, Jan.-June 1975 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and reports, July-Dec. 1975 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and reports, Jan.-May 1976 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and reports, June-Nov. 1976 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and reports, Feb. 1977 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and reports, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Political surveillance, miscellany, 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- SERIES III: SUBJECT AND ORGANIZATIONAL FILES, 1963-1979
  - Subseries A: Chicano Movement
    - August the 29th Movement, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Brown Berets, 1969-1972 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Casa Blanca Barrio, Riverside, California, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Catolicos Por La Raza, 1969-1970 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Chicanos in the media, 1969-1977 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Chicanos Unidos, El Paso, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Community development in Los Angeles, 1972-1978 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Community organizations. "Revised Directory of Organizations in South and East Los Angeles, Jan. 20,1969" (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Community-police relations, 1970-1977 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Community-police relations, Jacobo Hernandez Rodriguez, 1971-1977 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Community-police relations, newsclippings, 1969-1977 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Coors Beer Boycott, 1973-1977 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - General: flyers, pamphlets, 1974-1978 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - La Raza Unida Party, 1971-1977 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - La Raza Unida Party, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Mexican American history and culture, 1968-1973 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Mexican American history and culture, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Mexican American history and culture, 1976 (1) (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Mexican American history and culture, 1976 (2) (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Mexican American history and culture, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Mexican American history and culture, n.d. (1) (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Mexican American history and culture, n.d. (2) (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Mexican American history and culture, bibliographies, 1972-1975 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Mexican American history and culture, poetry, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous organizations, 1970-1977 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Newsclippings, 1968-1978 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Prensa Sembradora, Oakland, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Racism, articles, 1967-1977 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Reies Tijerina/Alianza Federal de los Pueblos Unidos, 1967-1969 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Rubén Salazar's death, East Los Angeles riots, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Teatro Movimiento Primavera; Teatro Nacional de Aztlan (TENAZ), ca. 1976-1977 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Women's issues, 1974-1977 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Subseries B: Education and Chicano Student Activism
    - Alan Bakke Case, legal documents, 1976-1978 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Alan Bakke Case, miscellany, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Alan Bakke Case, National Committee to Overturn the Bakke Decision, 1977-1978 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Alan Bakke Case, press releases and newsclippings, 1976-1978 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Alan Bakke Case, statements and reports, 1976-1977 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Alan Bakke Case, Statewide Conference on Minority Admissions, "Implications of the Bakke Case," 1977 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Articles, 1965-1971 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Articles, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Articles, 1973-1977 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Chicano curriculum materials, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Miscellany, 1963-1975 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Preschool facilities, 1972-1977 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - School busing, ca. 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Statement and Reports, 1968-1977 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Statements and Reports, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - University of California, Berkeley, Chicano Studies, 1971-1974 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - University of California, Berkeley, Riverside, student organization meeting, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - University of California, Berkeley, Santa Barbara, El Congreso, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - University of Southern California, Centro Chicano and MEChA, 1973-1977 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Subseries C: Papers of Jorge ("Coky") Rodriguez
    - California State University, Los Angeles, 1968-1977 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Castro, Sal, newsclippings, 1968-1969 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Chicano schools, 1970-1972 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Conferences and seminars, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - East Los Angeles College, 1969-1977 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - East Los Angeles College, Upward Bound, 1976-1977 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Ephemera, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Flyers, miscellaneous groups, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Garfield High School, Los Angeles, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Legal documents, 1970-1977 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Los Angeles School District, 1969-1972 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - MEChA-Carnalismo, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Notes, 1969-1977 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Notes, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Roosevelt High School, Los Angeles, 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Student movements, other high schools, 1968-1974 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - United Mexican American students, ca. 1970 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Subseries D: Immigration Reform
    - Carter Plan, ca. 1977 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence with U.S. consuls concerning immigration, May-Aug. 1972 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence with U.S. consuls concerning immigration, Sept. 1972-1977 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Drafts and notes, 1977-1978 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Notes on INS Commissioner Leonel Castillo, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Press releases, 1975-1977 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Publicity file, 1972-1976 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Reports, statements, 1976-1977 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Rodino Bill, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Teach-in Kit on the Undocumented Worker and Economic Crisis, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Subseries E: Organizations in which CASA Participated
    - Coalition Against the Rodino Bill, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Coalition to Stop Repressive Immigration Legislation, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Comité Obrero en Defensa de los Indocumentados in Lucha (CODIL), 1976-1978 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - July 4th Coalition, 1976-1977 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - National Campaign of Solidarity with the Immigrant Worker, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - National Coalition for Fair Immigration Laws and Practices, correspodence, 1977-1978 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - National Coalition for Fair Immigration Laws and Practices, internal evaluations, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - National Coalition for Fair Immigration Laws and Practices, mailing lists, notes, 1977-1978 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - National Coalition for Fair Immigration Laws and Practices, position papers, reports, 1976-1978 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - National Coalition for Fair Immigration Laws and Practices, publicity file, 1973-1978 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Subseries F: CASA Reference Files
    - Academic reports on immigration, 1965-1978 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - American Committee for Protection of Foreign Born, 1975-1978 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - California Conference on Immigration and Public Policy, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Cornelius Report on illegal immigration, 1976-1977 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Health care for illegal immigrants, 1976-1979 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Immigration law, analyses of legislation, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Immigration law, Centro de Immigracion, Georgetown University, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Immigration law, Illinois Migrant Council v. Pilliod, et. al., U.S. District Court opinion, Appeals court decision, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Immigration law, Illinois Migrant Council v. Vandersall, U.S. District Court complaint, 3 1976 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Immigration law, Legal Aid Foundation of Los Angeles, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Immigration law, miscellany, 1975-1978 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Immigration law, National Center for the Study of Aliens' Rights, 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Immigration law, National Lawyers Guild, "Immigration Newsletter," 1974-1977 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Immigration law, Rubio v. Superior Court of California, amici curiae brief, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Immigration law, Torres-Guerrero v. INS, brief, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous organizations, correspondence, press releases, statements, 1974-1979 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous organizations, meeting information, 1973-1977 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous organizations, publicity, 1975-1977 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Immigration law, reports and position papers, 1975-1977 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - National Chicano/Latino Conference, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews, Conference on Employment of Aliens, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Newsclippings, 1967-1976 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Newsclippings, 1977-1979 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Organized labor, statements on immigration policy, 1973-1976 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - United States Government, 1974-1978 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - United States Government, Dept. of Justice, Immigration and Naturalization Service, 1974-1977 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - United States Government, Dept. of Labor, 1975-1977 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - United States Government, Texts of immigration bills, 1973-1977 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Subseries G: Jose-Jacques Medina Deportation Case
    - Medina Defense Committee, correspondence, general, 1976-1977 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Medina Defense Committee, correspondence, Immigration and Naturalization Service, 1975-1977 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Medina Defense Committee, evidence supporting Medina's asylum request, correspondence, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Medina Defense Committee, evidence supporting Medina's asylum request, legal documents, 1973-1977 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Medina Defense Committee, evidence supporting Medina's asylum request, newsclippings, 1974-1976 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Medina Defense Committee, evidence supporting Medina's asylum request, statements by Medina, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Medina Defense Committee, legal documents, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Medina Defense Committee, legal staff, memoranda, 1975-1978 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Medina Defense Committee, Liberty Hill Foundation Grant, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Medina Defense Committee, list of possible witnesses, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Medina Defense Committee, minutes, notes, 1976-1977 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Medina Defense Committee, newsclippings about Medina, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Medina Defense Committee, petitions supporting Medina, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Medina Defense Committee, press releases, 1976-1977 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Medina Defense Committee, publicity file, 1976-1977 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Medina Trial, legal documents, 1976-Feb. 1977 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Medina Trial, legal documents, May-June 1977 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Medina Trial, legal documents, July-Dec. 1977 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Medina Trial, legal documents,.- Feb. 1978 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Medina Trial, legal documents, Exhibits A-W, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Medina Trial, legal documents, transcript of hearings, May-Sept. 1976 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Medina Trial, notes on strategy, ca. 1976 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Medina Trial, related cases, 1975-1977 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Subseries H: Los Tres del Barrio Narcotics Case
    - Community Concern Corporation, 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, Fernandez, Juan Ramon, 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Ortiz Sanchez, Alberto, 1973-1976 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Sanchez, Rodolfo Peña, 1972-1979 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Drug abuse, 1972-1974 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - National Committee to Free Los Tres, drafts of articles, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - National Committee to Free Los Tres, minutes, 1973-1975 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - National Committee to Free Los Tres, notes and miscellany, 1974-1975 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - National Committee to Free Los Tres, petitions, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - National Committee to Free Los Tres, publicity file, 1971-1976 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - National Committee to Free Los Tres, reports and statements, 1974-1975 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - National Committee to Free Los Tres, roll sheets, 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - National Committee to Free Los Tres, Sin Cadenas (newsletter), 1974-1975 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - United States of America v. Juan Ramón Fernandez, Alberto Ortiz Sanchez, Rudolfo Peña Sanchez, (U.S. District Court, Central District of California, Los Angeles, 8778), amicus curiae briefs, 1973, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - National Committee to Free Los Tres, legal documents concerning bail, 1970-1975 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - National Committee to Free Los Tres, reporters transcript of proceedings, Nov. 2, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - National Committee to Free Los Tres, reporters transcript of proceedings, Nov. 4, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - National Committee to Free Los Tres, reporters transcript of proceedings, Nov. 9, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - National Committee to Free Los Tres, reporters transcript of proceedings, Nov. 10, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - National Committee to Free Los Tres, reporters transcript of proceedings, Nov. 11, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Juan Ramón Fernandez, Alberto Ortiz Sanchez, Rodolfo Peña Sanchez v. United States of America (U.S. Court of Appeal, Ninth Circuit, San Francisco, 72-2088, 72-1408,72-2089), appellants' consolidated opening brief, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - National Committee to Free Los Tres, reporters transcript of proceedings, appellants' motion for permission to travel out of state, Mar. 15, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - National Committee to Free Los Tres, reporters transcript of proceedings, appellants' reply brief, ca. 1974 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - National Committee to Free Los Tres, reporters transcript of proceedings, appellee's brief, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - National Committee to Free Los Tres, reporters transcript of proceedings, opposition to appellants' motion, ca. 1974 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Subseries I: Protest and Political Movements (United States)
    - Anti-Vietnam War movement, 1975-1977 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Black protest, 1969-1977 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - California Originals Strike, ca. 1975-1976 (Box 39, Folder 1)